Guide to the Stanford University, Bing Overseas Studies Program, Records SC0117
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Bing Overseas Studies Program, records
1955-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Bing Overseas Studies Programs
SC0117
112.25 Linear Feet
Records pertain to the administration of the office at Stanford and the overseas campuses in Great Britain, Italy, Austria, France, Germany, Spain, Mexico, and other locations.
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use.
Acquisition Information
Administrative transfers, Overseas Studies, 1974-2016.
Administrative History
The Overseas Studies Office was established in 1958, and Robert A. Walker, a professor of political science at Stanford University and chairman of the Committee on General Studies, was appointed director. The first campus was set up in Beutelsbach, German in 1958 and shortly thereafter, in October of 1960 two additional locations in Tours, France, and Florence, Italy, were opened. Later, as demand grew, centers were opened in Britain at Harlaxton in 1966, in Austria in October 1966, and at Salamanca, Spain in October 1968.
These study programs proved inordinately popular until the late 1960s, when enrollments began to decline. In August of 1973, Mark Mancall, formerly a professor of history at Stanford, took over as director of the program with a difficult task ahead of him. He was faced with declining enrollments, rising costs overseas, and a budget cut by more than a third as part of the university's three-year belt-tightening program instituted in 1975. In addition, many of the programs were drawing increasing criticism regarding academic integrity, academic relevance to the particular locale, and methods of selecting professor for faculty positions. Under Mancall's leadership, the programs became more community-based with students living in a variety of housing options, rather than based around a single campus-building, and new programs were opened in Haifa and Mexico City.
Subsequent directors included Tom Heller, Russell Berman, Amos Nur, Norman Naimark, and Robert Sinclair. The program was renamed the Bing Overseas Studies Program in 2005.
Scope and Content of Collection
Records pertain to the administration of the office at Stanford and the overseas campuses in Great Britain, Italy, Austria, France, Germany, Spain, Mexico, and other locations and include correspondence, memoranda, financial records, minutes, academic records, orientation handbooks, and photographs. Also includes architectural drawings and insurance inventory and valuations of pictures and furnishings in Harlaxton Manor, Grafton, Stanford's first "Stanford-in-Britain" campus.
Foreign study.; Harlaxton Manor -- Grantham (Lincolnshire).; Walker, Robert A.; Stanford University. Bing Overseas Studies Programs; Kornberg, Roger D.; Stanford University. Office of Overseas Studies Programs; Mancall, Mark
- Records, Series 1
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-29/1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-30/1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-31/1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7-16-31/1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4-16-30/1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-16/1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/17-31/1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-16/1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/17-30/1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-16/1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/17-31/1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-16/1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/17-30/1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-16/1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/17-31/1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-16/1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/17-31/1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-16/1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/17-25/1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/26-31/1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-30/1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/15-31/1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-30/1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-16/1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/17-31/1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-16/1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/17-28/1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cables, Outgoing 1/1971-8/1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cables, Incoming 1/1971-8/1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cables, Incoming and Outgoing 9/1973-9/1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Cables, Incoming and Outgoing 9/1974-9/1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cables, Incoming and Outgoing 10/1975-12/1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cables, Incoming and Outgoing 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cables, Incoming 6-12/1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Cables, Outgoing 6-12/1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cables, Incoming 1/1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cables, Outgoing 1/1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Mail Log 4-8/1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Mail Log 9-12/1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Mail Log 1-8/1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-31/1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-16/1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/17-30/1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, Tours and Vienna Campuses 1960-1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1958 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1961-5/1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-8/31/1961 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1961-1/1962 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2-5/1962 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6-8/1962 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9-12/1962 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1961-5/1962 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6-8/1962 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1962-1/1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1-4/1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5-8/1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9-12/1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1-4/1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5-8/1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9-12/1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1-4/1964 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5-8/1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9-12/1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9-12/1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1-4/1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1-4/1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5-7/1965 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5-9/1965 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8-10/1965 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11-12/1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1966 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1965-1/1966 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1966 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1966 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1966 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1966 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1966 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1966 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/166 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1967 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1968 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1968 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1968 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-30/1968 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1968 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1968 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1968 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1968 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1968 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1968 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1968 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1968 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1969 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-30/1969 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1969 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1969 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1969 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1969 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1969 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1969 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/15-31/1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-14/1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/15-28/1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-14/1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/15-31/1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-14/1970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/15-30/1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-14/1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/15-31/1970 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-14/1970 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/15-30/1970 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-14/1970 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/15-31/1970 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-14/1970 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/15-31/1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-14/1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/15-30/1970 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-14/1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/15-31/1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-14/1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/15-30/1970 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-14/1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/15-31/1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Cables, Outgoing 1-12/1970 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-14/1971 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/15-31/1971 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-14/1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/15-28/1971 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-14/1971 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/15-31/1971 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-14/1971 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/15-30/1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-14/1971 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/15-31/1971 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-14/1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/15-30/1971 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-14/1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/15-31/1971 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-14/1971 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/15-31/1971 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-14/1971 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/15-30/1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-14/1971 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/15-31/1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-14/1971 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/15-31/1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-14/1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/15-31/1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-14/1972 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/15-31/1972 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-14/1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/15-29/1972 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-14/1972 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/15-31/1972 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-14/1972 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/15-30/1972 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-14/1972 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/15-30/1972 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-14/1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/15-30/1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-14/1972 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/15-31/1972 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-14/1972 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/15-31/1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-14/1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/15-30/1972 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-14/1972 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/15-31/1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)